A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, President, Karen Davis papers, SG 2 FA1127
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meetings and Program Files, 5; 34.16 Cubic Feet
  - Karen Davis Congratulations - A-D, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 708)
  - Karen Davis Congratulations - D-G, 1992-1995 (Box 82, Folder 709)
  - Karen Davis Congratulations - H-M (Box 82, Folder 710)
  - Karen Davis Congratulations - N-R (Box 82, Folder 711)
  - Karen Davis Congratulations - S-Z (Box 82, Folder 712)
  - Association of Academic Health Centers Annual Meeting, Tucson, AZ, 2000 October 4 (Box 82, Folder 713)
  - Massachusetts Medical Society, 2000 October 28 (Box 83, Folder 714)
  - Jacobs Institute - Margaret E. Mahoney Annual Symposium, 2000 September 22 (Box 83, Folder 715)
  - Harkness Fellows in Health Care Policy Dinner, 2000 September 26 (Box 83, Folder 716)
  - UCF - Health Care Challenges, 2000 December 12 (Box 83, Folder 717)
  - ABCD Program Direction, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 718)
  - Duke University - Private Sector Conference, Academic Health Center in the 21st Century, 1995 April (Box 83, Folder 719)
  - Task Force on Academic Health Centers, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 720)
  - Advancing the Well-Being of Elderly People Advisory Committee, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 721)
  - Adolescent Boys Health Survey, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 722)
  - Adolescent Girls Health Survey, 1994-1997 (Box 84, Folder 723)
  - Alberta Heritage Foundation for Medical Research, 1998 October (Box 84, Folder 724)
  - Congressional Staff Retreat - Bipartisan Health Solutions, 1998 January (Box 84, Folder 725)
  - Congressional Staff Retreat, 1998-2000 (Box 84, Folder 726)
  - Health Sector Assembly, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 727)
  - Atlantic Fellowship, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 728)
  - Axford Fellowships in Public Policy, 1996 (Box 85, Folder 729)
  - Queta Bond, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 730)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1995-1998 (Box 85, Folder 731)
  - Carter Symposium on Mental Health Policy, Atlanta, GA, 1995 November 15 (Box 85, Folder 732)
  - Casey Journalism Center, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 733)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 734)
  - Joe Califano, 1992-1999 (Box 85, Folder 735)
  - Health Care Reform Presidential Candidates, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 736)
  - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board Task Force on Clinton Health Care Plan, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 737)
  - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board Task Force on Clinton Health Care Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 738-739)
  - Grantmakers in Health, 1996-1999 (Box 86, Folder 740)
  - Grantmakers in Health, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 741)
  - Grantmakers in Health, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 742-743)
  - Harkness Fellows, 1998-2000 (Box 87, Folder 744-745)
  - Harkness Fellows, 1995-1998 (Box 87, Folder 746)
  - Harkness Fellows - Placement, 1995 January 17 (Box 87, Folder 747)
  - Harkness Fellows Seminar, Pittsburgh, PA, 1992 August 17 (Box 87, Folder 748)
  - Harkness Fellows, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 749)
  - Harkness Fellows - London, 1994-1995 (Box 87, Folder 750-751)
  - Harkness Fellows - U. S. Panel of Ambassadors, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 752)
  - Harkness Symposium 1995, 1995 May (Box 88, Folder 753)
  - Harkness Fellows Orientation 1995, 1995 August (Box 88, Folder 754)
  - Harkness Fellows New Zealand-Australia 1995-1996 (Box 88, Folder 755-756)
  - John A. Hartford Foundation, 1994-1999 (Box 89, Folder 757)
  - Melbourne, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 758)
  - Meeting Notes - Miscellaneous, 1994-1996 (Box 89, Folder 759)
  - 1999 Margaret E. Mahoney (MEM) Symposium (Box 89, Folder 760)
  - 1998 Margaret E. Mahoney (MEM) Symposium, 1998-1999 (Box 89, Folder 761)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney (MEM) Meetings - Notes, 1993-1996 (Box 90, Folder 762)
  - 1996 Margaret E. Mahoney (MEM) Symposium, 1996 May (Box 90, Folder 763)
  - 1995 Margaret E. Mahoney (MEM) Symposium, 1995 May (Box 90, Folder 764)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney (MEM) Meetings, 1994-1998 (Box 90, Folder 765)
  - 1998 Mentoring Symposium (Box 90, Folder 766)
  - Minority Health Meetings, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 767)
  - Minority Health Meetings, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 768)
  - National Alliance for Caregiving, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 769)
  - Nathan Cummings Foundation, 1997-1999 (Box 91, Folder 770-771)
  - National Bipartisan Commission on the Future of Medicare, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 772)
  - National Committee for Quality Health Care, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 773)
  - 1998 National Survey of Workers Health (Box 92, Folder 774)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 775)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 92, Folder 776)
  - New York Community Trust, 1993-1995 (Box 92, Folder 777)
  - Nursing Home Restraints Program Review, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 778)
  - Nuffield Trust, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 779)
  - New York State - New York City Health, 1994-1998 (Box 92, Folder 780)
  - Office of Public Health, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 781)
  - Packard Foundation, 1995 (Box 93, Folder 782)
  - Primary Care Development Corporation, 1998-2001 (Box 93, Folder 783)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health, 1992-1993 (Box 93, Folder 784)
  - Picker-Commonwealth Fund Scholars Program Annual Meeting 1995 (Box 93, Folder 785)
  - Rice Symposium 1998 (Box 93, Folder 786)
  - Royal Society of the Arts (RSA), 1996 (Box 93, Folder 787)
  - Commonwealth Fund's 75th Anniversary Celebration, 1992-1994 (Box 93, Folder 788)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1994-2002 (Box 93, Folder 789)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center - Publications, 1989-1992 (Box 94, Folder 790)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1983-1997 (Box 94, Folder 791)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 792)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 94, Folder 793)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 94, Folder 794)
  - Staff Seminars, 1992-1995 (Box 94, Folder 795)
  - Sydney 1999 (Box 94, Folder 796-797)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance, 1999-2000 (Box 95, Folder 798)
  - Testimony - Managed Care - H. R. 820 - Karen Davis, 1997 October 28 (Box 95, Folder 799)
  - Toronto 1999 (Box 95, Folder 800)
  - Jim Morgan, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 801)
  - United Hospital Fund, 1992-1998 (Box 95, Folder 802-803)
  - United Hospital Fund, 1992-1994 (Box 96, Folder 804)
  - Dorothy Rice Symposium, University of California-San Francisco, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 805)
  - University of Virginia Health Sciences Center, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 806)
  - Urban Institute, 1995-1997 (Box 96, Folder 807)
  - White House Conference on Aging, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 808)
  - Whitehead Institute - Gerald R. Fink, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 809)
  - Commission on Women's Health, 1992-1995 (Box 96, Folder 810)
  - Women's Economic Leadership Summit, 1997 April (Box 96, Folder 811)
  - Commission on Women's Health, 1997-1999 (Box 97, Folder 812)
  - Women's Health Program Review, 1996-1998 (Box 97, Folder 813)
  - Women's Health Research and Education Institute (WREI) - Dooley, 1993-1998 (Box 97, Folder 814)
  - Young African-American Male Survey, 1993-1995 (Box 97, Folder 815)
  - Clinton Health Care Reform, 1993-1998 (Box 97, Folder 816)
  - Clinton Health Care Reform, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 817-819)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1995-1998 (Box 98, Folder 820)
  - Commonwealth Fund Foundation "Niche" Project, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 821)
  - Commonwealth Fund Staff Retreat 1998, Princeton, NJ (Box 98, Folder 822)
  - Commonwealth Fund Staff Retreat 2000 (Box 98, Folder 823)
  - Foundation Information (Box 99, Folder 824)
  - Council on the Economic Impact of Health Care Reform, 1994-1999 (Box 99, Folder 825-826)
  - Denmark 1998, 1998 April (Box 99, Folder 827)
  - Department of Health and Human Services, 1993-1999 (Box 99, Folder 828)
  - Harvard Medical School, 1992-1998 (Box 100, Folder 829)
  - Havard Fellowship in Minority Health Policy, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 830)
  - Health Care Financing Administration, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 831)
  - Health Care Reform Advisory Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 100, Folder 832)
  - 1999 Health Sector Assembly - American Medical Association (AMA) (Box 100, Folder 833)
  - Health Services Improvement Fund, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 834)
  - Independent Sector - Margaret E. Mahoney, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 835)
  - International Symposium on Health Policy, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 836)
  - International Symposium on Health Policy (Box 101, Folder 837)
  - Jacobs Institute of Women's Health, 1999 (Box 101, Folder 838)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Sommer, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 839)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Eggleston-Wehr, 1992-1993 (Box 101, Folder 840)
  - Bipartisan Conference, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 841)
  - Lasker Foundation - Funding First, 1999-2000 (Box 101, Folder 842)
  - London 1998 (Box 101, Folder 843)
  - London - Ditchley 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 102, Folder 844)
  - London 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 102, Folder 845-846)
  - Louis Harris and Associates, 1992-1998 (Box 102, Folder 847)
  - LBJ School of Public Affairs, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 848)
  - Healthy Steps 1999 (Box 103, Folder 849-850)
  - Healthy Steps 1998 (Box 103, Folder 851-853)
  - Healthy Steps 1997 (Box 104, Folder 854)
  - Healthy Steps 1996 (Box 104, Folder 855)
  - Healthy Steps 1995 (Box 104, Folder 856)
  - Healthy Steps 1994 (Box 104, Folder 857)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 104, Folder 858)
  - The Claude Pepper Foundation, Inc. (Box 104, Folder 859)
  - Pew Charitable Trusts, 1995-1998 (Box 104, Folder 860)
  - Philadelphia Futures, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 861)
  - Harvey Picker, 1998-2000 (Box 105, Folder 862)
  - Camden 1999 (Box 105, Folder 863)
  - Special Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 864)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 April (Box 105, Folder 865)
  - Board of Directors - Committee Meetings, 1998 July (Box 105, Folder 866)
  - Board of Directors - Committee Meetings, 1998 July (Box 106, Folder 867)
  - Board of Directors Meetings, 1998 November (Box 106, Folder 868-869)
  - Board of Directors Meetings, 1999 July (Box 106, Folder 870)
  - Board of Directors Meetings, 1999 July (Box 107, Folder 871)
  - Board of Directors - Committee Meetings, 1999 October (Box 107, Folder 872)
  - Board of Directors - Nominating Committee, 1997 Fall (Box 107, Folder 873)
  - Board of Directors - Nominating Committee (Box 107, Folder 874)
  - Board of Directors - Nominating Committee, 1990s (Box 108, Folder 875-877)
  - Board of Directors - Nominating Committee, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 878)
  - Board of Directors - Nominating Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 108, Folder 879)
  - Board Meeting Notes, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 880)
  - Board Meeting Notes, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 881)
  - Board Meeting Notes, 1994 (Box 109, Folder 882)
  - Board Meeting Notes, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 883)
  - Board Meeting Notes, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 884)
  - Board Meeting Notes, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 885)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 1996-1998 (Box 109, Folder 886-887)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 888)
  - Karen Davis Desk Calendars, 1994-1995 (Box 110, Folder 889)
  - Karen Davis Desk Calendars, 1996-1997 (Box 110, Folder 890)
  - Karen Davis Desk Calendars, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 891)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 1995 July (Box 110, Folder 892)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 1998 November (Box 111, Folder 893)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 1999 April (Box 111, Folder 894)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 1999 July (Box 111, Folder 895)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 1999 November (Box 111, Folder 896)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 2000 April (Box 111, Folder 897)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 2000 July (Box 111, Folder 898)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 2000 November (Box 111, Folder 899)
  - Executive Management Meeting Agendas, 2001-2002 (Box 111, Folder 900)
  - Foundation Information (Box 112, Folder 901)
  - John Craig Talking Points, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 902)
  - Regulation of the Independent Sector, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 903)
  - Inside the Boardroom - William G. Bowen, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 904)
  - Briefing New Directors, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 905)
  - Board By-Laws, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 906)
  - Governance is Governance, Kenneth N. Dayton, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 907)
  - Governance Stucture, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 908)
  - Association for Health Services Research (AHSR), 1996-2001 (Box 112, Folder 909)
  - Baxter Allegiance Foundation Prize (Awarded to Karen Davis), 2000 (Box 112, Folder 910)
  - Ray Marshall Advisory Committee, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 911)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health - Health Advisory Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 112, Folder 912)
  - Association for Health Services Research (AHSR), 1996-2000 (Box 112, Folder 913)
  - Association for Health Services Research (AHSR), 1996-1998 (Box 113, Folder 914-916)
  - Health Related Reports, Articles, Surveys, 2002-2003 (Box 113, Folder 917-918)
  - Health Related Reports, Articles, Surveys, 2002-2003 (Box 114, Folder 919)
  - AHRQ National Advisory Council Meeting, 2001 (Box 114, Folder 920)
  - AAMC Group, Keynote Speaker, 2020 Vision, 2003 April 27 (Box 114, Folder 921)
  - Dirigo Health, Maine, 2003 (Box 114, Folder 922)
  - Board Recruitment and Lists, 1988-1993 (Box 115, Folder 923)
  - Institute for Health Care Improvement (IHI) - Health Care Quality Project, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 924)
  - OECD "Measuring Up" Conference, 2001 November 5-7 (Box 115, Folder 925)
  - Consumer Driven Health Plans (CDHP), AcademyHealth, The Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 115, Folder 926)
  - Board of Directors - Nominating Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 116, Folder 927)
  - Board of Directors - Nominating Committee, 2001-2003 (Box 116, Folder 928)
  - National Advisory Council - Agency for Health Care Research and Quality, 2002 July 26 (Box 116, Folder 929)
  - Council on Health Care Economics and Policy - The Ninth Princeton Conference - Can Health Care Be Contained, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 930)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) - Philanthropy Session, Pocantico, NY, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 931)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) - Philanthropy Sessions, Pocantico, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 117, Folder 932)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) Meetings, 1997-2000 (Box 117, Folder 933)
  - Small Grants and Board Level Grant Requests and Appreciation Letter (ACL), 2003 (Box 117, Folder 934)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Criteria, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 935)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 2003 (Box 117, Folder 936)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 937-938)
  - Karen Davis Chronological Files, 2000-2003 (Box 118, Folder 939-942)
  - Karen Davis Chronological Files, 2003-2004 (Box 119, Folder 943-945)
  - Surveys and Project Files, 1992-1994; 1996-2002 (Box 119, Folder 946-947)
  - Surveys and Project Files, 2002-2003 (Box 120, Folder 948-949)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, 1998 October 2 (Box 120, Folder 950)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, 2000 July 17-18 (Box 120, Folder 951)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2000 December 7-8 (Box 121, Folder 952)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, 2001 April 26-27 (Box 121, Folder 953)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, 2001 July 12-13 (Box 121, Folder 954-955)
  - Child Health Services Research Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 2001 June 9 (Box 121, Folder 956)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2001 October 25-26 (Box 122, Folder 957)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes Nuffield Trust, 2000 June (Box 122, Folder 958)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 959)
  - Healthy Steps - National Advisory Committee Meeting, 1999 May 25-26 (Box 122, Folder 960)
  - Healthy Steps - National Advisory Committee Meeting, 2000 October 24-25 (Box 122, Folder 961)
  - Healthy Steps - National Advisory Committee Meeting, 2001 October (Box 123, Folder 962)
  - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 2004 September 9 (Box 123, Folder 963-965)
  - International Symposium on Health Policy, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 966-967)
  - Operations and Personnel Handbook, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 968)
    Restricted - Personnel material
  - 2004 Commonwealth Fund Annual Album (Box 124)
  - 2005 Commonwealth Fund Annual Album (Box 124)
  - The Commonwealth Fund - An Historical Sketch, by Barry C. Smith (Box 125, Folder 969)
  - Patient Centered Care Project for Managed Care - Survey of Experiences, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 970-972)
  - Final Reports of the Health Reform Technical Work Groups, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 973)
  - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 2003 (Box 126, Folder 974)
  - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 2002 (Box 126, Folder 975)
  - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 2001 (Box 126, Folder 976)
  - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 2000 (Box 126, Folder 977)
  - Dirigio Health Planning Meeting, 2003 (Box 126, Folder 978)
  - Proposals to Include Health Care Quality - Hillary Clinton, 2004 January 12 (Box 126, Folder 979)
  - Bush and Kerry Health Care Proposals, 2004 September (Box 127, Folder 980)
  - Medicaid Commission - Karen Davis Notes, 2004 January 22 (Box 127, Folder 981)
  - IOM Rapid Advance - Demontration Projects Committee, 2002 (Box 127, Folder 982)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 1999-2002 (Box 127, Folder 983)
  - Governor's Health Care Reform Working Group, 2004 November (Box 127, Folder 984)
  - Medicaid Roundtable, 2004 (Box 127, Folder 985)
  - Patrick Kennedy Briefing, 2003 September 25 (Box 127, Folder 986)
  - PDF Meeting Notes FY2000, 1999-2000 (Box 127, Folder 987-988)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures, Washington, D.C., 2003 June 6 (Box 127, Folder 989)
  - Breaux Panel-NASI Reception, Washington, D.C., 2003 June 11 (Box 128, Folder 990)
  - Personal-Alliance Briefing, Rhode Island, 2003 June 14-16 (Box 128, Folder 991)
  - AcademyHealth Annual Research Meeting, Nashville, TN, 2003 June 26-29 (Box 128, Folder 992)
  - Havard School of Public Health - Center for Health Communication Review (Box 128, Folder 993)
  - Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy Annual Meeting 2003 (Box 128, Folder 994)
  - Harvard University - Emerging Health Care Leadership Project (Box 128, Folder 995)
  - 2001 Quality Survey (Box 128, Folder 996)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, 2003 February (Box 128, Folder 997)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2003 April 3-4 (Box 128, Folder 998)
  - Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured - Commission Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2003 April 3-4 (Box 129, Folder 999)
  - Minority Health in America Book, 2000 (Box 129, Folder 1000)
  - 1992 Contract Report to Centers for Disease Control (CDC) - Health Care Reform and Preventive Services (Box 129, Folder 1001-1002)
  - 1998 Alice Hersch Memorial Lecture, 1998 June (Box 129, Folder 1003)
  - Medicare Modernization Meeting, 2001 August 21 (Box 129, Folder 1004)
  - Commission on Women's Health, Washington, D. C., 1998 January 28 (Box 130, Folder 1005)
  - Healthy Steps - National Evaluation Working Paper Series, Vol. 1, No. 7 (Box 130, Folder 1006-1007)
  - Healthy Steps - Strategies for Change - Child Development in Primary Care for Young Children (Box 130, Folder 1008-1009)
  - National Summit on Medical Errors and Patient Safety, 2000 September (Box 130, Folder 1010)
  - National Summit on Medical Errors and Patient Safety, 2000 September (Box 131, Folder 1011)
  - 1978 Chapman Consultations on Commonwealth Fund Programs (Box 131, Folder 1012)
  - Harkness Fellowships: A Review and Proposal, 1983 (Box 131, Folder 1013)
  - Communications and Information Program Study, 1983 (Box 131, Folder 1014)
  - Commonwealth Fund Fellowships - Medicine, 1984 (Box 131, Folder 1015)
  - Karen Davis - Prospective Board Chair Workbook, 1993 (Box 131, Folder 1016)
  - Review of the Harkness Fellowships, 1925-1974 (Box 131, Folder 1017)
  - Program Staff Retreat, 1994 May 10 (Box 131, Folder 1018)
  - The Health Security Act of 1993 - Working Group Draft (Box 132, Folder 1019)
  - The Health Security Act of 1993 - August 10 Draft Plan (Box 132, Folder 1020-1021)
  - Analysis of the Health Security Act, 1993 November (Box 132, Folder 1022-1023)
  - Helene Kaplan, 1990-2003 (Box 133, Folder 1024-1025)
  - Charles Sanders (Box 133, Folder 1026)
  - Top Ten Health Policy Stories 2004 (Box 133, Folder 1027)
  - Boston SamTHIER Meeting, Lunch with Jim Mongan, 2005 March 1 (Box 133, Folder 1028)
  - Call for David Helms, Re: AcademyHealth Invitational Meeting, 2004 June 1 (Box 133, Folder 1029)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Committee on the Future of Health Professions, 2004 April (Box 133, Folder 1030)
  - 2003 Successes, 2004 Goals, 2003-2004 (Box 133, Folder 1031)
  - Baxter Prize Selection (Box 133, Folder 1032)
  - Medicare Reform Ideas, 2003 November 5 (Box 133, Folder 1033)
  - Lawrence Huntington, 2003 (Box 133, Folder 1034)
  - Robert O'Neil (Box 134, Folder 1035)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 2004 (Box 134, Folder 1036)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 134, Folder 1037)
  - Charles Sanders (Box 134, Folder 1038)
  - Health Care Reform Papers (Box 134, Folder 1039-1040)
  - Denmark 1998 - Danish Health Care (Box 135, Folder 1041-1044)
  - Denmark 1998 - Danish Health Care (Box 136, Folder 1045-1046)
  - The Open Mind with Karen Davis, The Quality of American Health Care, 2003 September 26; 29 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11732)
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - The Open Mind: Mack Lipkin, Jr, Talking to the Doctor: Listening to the Patient, Part I and II, 2002 December 3; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11733)
  - The Open Mind: Dr. Robin I. Stone, Caring for Our Elders, 2002 November 6; 29 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11734)
  - The Open Mind: Host: Richard D. Heffner, Guest: Dr. Neal Halfon, Child Rearing in America, 2003 May 22; 29 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11735)
  - External Review of Canadian Institutes of Health, 2006 (Box 136, Folder 1047-1049)
  - Pennyhill Park, 2003 (Box 137, Folder 1050)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 1051-1051A)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 2006 (Box 137, Folder 1052-1053)
  - New York City Mayor's Commission on Women's Issues (Box 137, Folder 1054)
  - New York City Mayor's Commission on Women's Issues (Box 138, Folder 1055-1058)
  - Foundation Executives Group Meeting, 2003 April 3-4 (Box 138, Folder 1059)
  - Foundation Executives Group Meeting, 2004 April (Box 138, Folder 1060)
  - Foundation Executives Group Meeting, 2004 February (Box 139, Folder 1061)
  - Trade Act Tax Credits for Health Care Meeting, Washington, D. C., 2004 April 26 (Box 139, Folder 1062)
  - Keynote Speech, VHA Annual Retreat, Phoenix, AZ, 2004 April 20 (Box 139, Folder 1063)
  - Harvard Spring Exercises, Boston, 2004 April 26 (Box 139, Folder 1064)
  - Lunch with Thomas Frieden, New York, 2004 June 24 (Box 139, Folder 1065)
  - LTC Talk, San Diego, CA, 2004 June 5 (Box 139, Folder 1066)
  - Women's Health Conference - Participants List, 2004 June (Box 139, Folder 1067)
  - AcademyHealth Annual Meeting, 2004 June (Box 139, Folder 1068-1069)
  - Harkness Seminar, 2004 (Box 140, Folder 1070)
  - Harkness Final Reporting Seminar, 2004 June 3-4 (Box 140, Folder 1071)
  - Academy Health Invitational Meeting, Washington, D. C., 2004 June 16 (Box 140, Folder 1072)
  - The Eleventh Princeton Conference, 2004 May 20-21 (Box 140, Folder 1073)
  - GHI Webcast, Washington, D. C., 2004 May 11 (Box 140, Folder 1074)
  - Foundation Executives Group Meeting, Pocantico, NY, 2004 May 6-7 (Box 140, Folder 1075)
  - Alliance for Health Reform, Washington, D. C., 2004 May 7 (Box 140, Folder 1076)